<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sam´s corner</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/samscorner/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sam´s corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:54:50 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/samscorner/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elitism ruins everything, and crusty old motorcycles rock!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/samscorner/posts/gs500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:54:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/samscorner/posts/gs500/</guid>
      <description>Motorcycles are cool, I think most people can agree on that. Yes, I know, they are noisy, dangerous, impractical etc. but still, there´s something about them that speak to a lot of people.&#xA;In the spring of 2024, having worked a few months as a grunt at a Slovenian tech company, I could for the first time in my life seriously consider buying a motorcycle. One weekend, a deal that I could not resist popped up: A newly serviced and inspected Suzuki GS500E for 14 000 SEK(~1300$).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I´m on the Internet!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/samscorner/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:40:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/samscorner/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>It´s about time this page gets launched. It´s been in the back of my head for a long time. Ever since I started watching this slightly alt-right feeling guy Luke Smith, I knew I needed my own website.&#xA;It became even more apparent when I, as I often do when my mental health is good, was rambling about something that I had researched to my girlfriend. After maybe half an hour of elaborate comparisons of motorcycle engine layouts, or the virtues of different sailboat rig types, or some other nonsense occupying 95% of my cognitive abilities, she turned to me(probably in despair), and said:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
