<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sam´s corner</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sam´s corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 12:43:09 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How/why should I document my life?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/documenting_your_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 12:43:09 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/documenting_your_life/</guid>
      <description>Journaling, mindfulness, mood scarves, photo albums, digital picture frames, gratefulness jars etc. The ways that we can store information about ousersevles today are seemingly endless. As I´m writing this in early january of 2025, I should really be tending to my &amp;ldquo;yearly archiving&amp;rdquo;. But as always when there are many ways to do something, I start to doubt if my way of doing it is right. So, to find a better way to go about things, or at least to alleviate my doubts about my system for now, I think we need to look more closely at the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The beautiful country with the horrific history</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bosnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 20:10:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bosnia/</guid>
      <description>Tl;dr We went to bosnia here´s a VIDEO of it.&#xA;In the fall of 2024, me and my partner were faced with a new and unfamiliar predicament. Not only were we part of the socio-economic group some people call D.I.N.K´s, my partner was also enjoying her first höstlov(fall holiday week) as a teacher. This needed an appropriate celebration, dog days were over and we were ready for the high life! We decided that a short vacation would be fitting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison is the thief of all joy, and crusty old motorcycles rock!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gs500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:54:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gs500/</guid>
      <description>Motorcycles. They are unnecessary, obnoxious, dangerous and anti-social. Despite all this(or maybe because of it?), many men build their identities around these mid life crisis machines.&#xA;In the spring of 2024, having worked a few months as a grunt at a Slovenian tech company, I could for the first time in my life seriously consider buying a motorcycle. One weekend, a deal that I could not resist popped up: A newly serviced and inspected Suzuki GS500E for 14 000 SEK(~1300$).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I´m on the Internet!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:40:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>It´s about time this page gets launched. It´s been in the back of my head for a long time. Ever since I started watching this slightly alt-right feeling guy Luke Smith, I knew I needed my own website.&#xA;It became even more apparent when I, as I often do when my mental health is good, was rambling about something that I had researched to my girlfriend. After maybe half an hour of elaborate comparisons of motorcycle engine layouts, or the virtues of different sailboat rig types, or some other nonsense occupying 95% of my cognitive abilities, she turned to me(probably in despair), and said:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
